egames.com 2006-04-21

# Privacy Statement

**Privacy Statement** **  
** eGames has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy rights of our online visitors and to the purchasers of our products. At eGames, we strive to help our customers protect their privacy while using our products and services. This privacy statement contains information about our website and our products, some of which may make use of your Internet connection. This privacy statement provides information about: what personally identifiable information of yours is collected; what organization is collecting the information; how the information is used; with whom the information may be shared; what choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information; and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. Please note that this policy relates only to websites or products developed and/ or maintained by eGames, Inc. This policy does not apply to websites or products developed and/or maintained by other companies to which we link or which provide services to our website. 

**Information Collected**  

On some pages of the eGames website, you can purchase products or register a product online. If you are purchasing a product online, the type of personal information collected includes:           

Name              
Address              
Email address              
Phone Number              
Credit Card Information           

If you register a product online, the type of personal information collected includes:           

Name              
Email address              
Address              
Product purchased              
Location of Purchase              
Your computer platform              
Age              
Gender              
Telephone Number 

**What Organizations Collect Information**

When you purchase a product online, you are providing the information identified above to eGames. 

We have contracted with two third party entities to provide our e-commerce shopping cart: 1) A host service, Visual Impact Productions, which provides server space and bandwidth availability and 2) Skipjack, a credit card processor. The host service maintains a secure database of customer information, including name, email and street address, telephone number, but excluding any credit card information. The credit card processor utilizes a customer's credit card information to process debits or credits to the customer's credit card account as necessary. Both entities maintain security measures designed to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your user data under their control. Both use physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect any personally identifiable data stored on their computers. Only authorized employees have access to the information you provide us. Listed are links to their respective privacy policies:[ http://www.skipjack.com/privacy/index.html ](http://www.skipjack.com/privacy/index.html%20)

When you register a product online, you are providing the information to Equifax Direct Marketing Solutions, Inc. (“Equifax”), an unaffiliated third party. For more information on the registration process and use of the information collected, click **[here](http://www.equifax.com/universal/privacy.shtml). **

**The Way Your Information Is Used  
  
**

The information you provide about yourself when placing an order is used by eGames and its third-party e-commerce providers to complete that order. The information may also be used by eGames to send promotional email messages, but only if you have agreed to receive future promotional messages when completing your order. **** Customers who buy products from the eGames website are shopping on a secure server, which encrypts all of the customer’s personal information including name, address and credit card number. Encryption is used to block access and use of this information in an unauthorized manner.  The eGames’ shopping cart uses Secure Socket Layers. This means that the data being sent to the eGames server from your browser is encrypted using high-level encryption technology.

**_Who Your Information is Shared With_**

When you register a product through Equifax, as described below, the personal information you provide in the registration form – name, address, etc. -- allows eGames and Equifax to inform you of additional special offers which may be forthcoming, and to send you coupons, or notify you of products and services of affiliates of Equifax that relate directly to your specific interests, hobbies or other information you have given. As part of the entry process, we give you the opportunity to decline to receive any communications from other parties to whom the information may be provided.

The data collected is used in the aggregate to give eGames and Equifax demographic information about the entire audience registering eGames products. eGames uses this information to better understand that audience and to improve our offerings to our customers. The data collected may also be disclosed by Equifax to unaffiliated third parties (companies that are not owned or controlled by us) for various business purposes, including marketing and joint business efforts for related and unrelated products and services. ****

**What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information**  

Users may opt out of receiving future notifications about new products and features by checking “no” at the bottom of the registration form or shopping cart. This option allows customers to purchase a product or register a product without receiving promotional notices. Registering through Equifax, as described below under the heading “Register,” does provide information to third parties. In order to “opt out” of sharing information with third parties, users should not register their products through Equifax.

**How You Can Access or Correct Your Information**

You can access your personally identifiable information that we collect online in our registration form by contacting our Customer Service Department at 215-750-6606 and pressing 5 (for our customer service department) or by email at [techpriority@egames.com](mailto:%20techpriority@egames.com).  You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information that you have submitted in a registration form by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**Register**

**  
** You can register products online to receive information about upcoming products and announcements. Information you submit when completing our online registration form will not be used for this purpose unless you indicate that you wish to receive such additional information when you fill out the registration form. We use the information from the registration form to better design our website, create better products, bring to market products that consumers are looking for, and, to the extent you have agreed, to send email messages notifying you of special offers and promotions. 

eGames has partnered with Equifax to handle our customer registration process. Through their proprietary technology, all new eGames products sold at retail and on our website will have an option for users to register their product at the time of installation. This registration is optional, and allows the user to send their registration information over the Internet or through traditional mail services. Equifax will also be collecting registration information from the eGames website registration page.

Equifax (NYSE:EFX), a 103-year-old S&P 500 company, enables and secures global commerce through its information management, marketing services, direct to consumer, commercial and authentication businesses. More information about Equifax, including their privacy policy, can be viewed at <http://www.equifax.com/>

**Cookies**  

What are cookies? Cookies are pieces of information – in the form of a small text file - that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive. The cookie transmits information back to the server that placed it, and most times can only be read by that server. Cookies can make Web-surfing easier for website visitors by saving the user’s preferences while at our site.

The use of cookies is an industry standard -- you'll find them at most major Web sites. By showing how and when visitors use a site, cookies help us see which areas of our website are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on the data collected by cookies such as the total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. We use the information from cookies to provide services better tailored to our users’ needs. 

We have two primary uses for cookies. First, we use them to specify unique preferences. Secondly, we use cookies to track website user trends and patterns. This helps us to better understand and improve areas of our website. You may also get cookies from third-party advertisers. eGames does not control these cookies. The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry. 

Most Internet browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. If you take affirmative steps to decline cookies, it will not impair your ability to browse our website, but you will not be able to sign up for an account or purchase products online unless cookies are accepted.

**Online Information Display**

**  
** All new eGames' products released between May 15, 2002 and December 1, 2003 contain a technology, the "Online Information Display", that can receive and display messages in the interface of your game. These messages may include product updates, patches, special offers and new product information from eGames. 

The end user will be asked if they wish to utilize this new feature during the installation of the product. No personally identifiable information of any kind is collected, and the feature may be turned off at any time in the game's main interface.

The online information display is a one-way website broadcast from www.eGames.com to the eGames software you are installing. It will present messages about your product, patches, updates, promotions, new products and other such information from our website, [www.eGames.com](http://www.egames.com/).

The way it works is that the software you are installing will use your existing Internet service connection to download very small messages in html (world wide web page) format from our server onto your computer, which are then displayed in the game's interface. This download interaction only occurs if you are connected to the Internet, and only when you start the eGames product you have purchased or downloaded. This interaction only occurs when you start the program, and no interaction occurs when the game is not running. If you are not connected to the Internet when you begin playing this game, no download will occur. These interactions typically are very small, and should not have a significant impact on your internet connection bandwidth, even for 56k telephone modem users. 

No information is collected or stored before, during or after this information display system functions. 

No third party software of any kind will be installed on your computer. The system works solely through the eGames software you have purchased or downloaded, in conjunction with our website, www.egames.com.. 

An existing Internet Service Provider (such as America Online, cable modem, DSL, etc.) is required for this service to function.

**Advertising Integrated into our Products**

Some older eGames applications make use of third-party software developed by Conducent Technologies, Inc. The software utility (sometimes referred to as the TimeSink, TSAD.DLL and/or TSADBOT.EXE utilities) was developed by Conducent to allow unattended updates of advertising messages to be displayed. The utility was designed to start up each time the computer is turned on, and then used the Internet connection to retrieve information from Conducent’s ad servers about what ads to display (and when) in order to refresh the displayed advertising from time to time. The utility had also sent other information to Conducent’s ad servers, including the computer’s operating system type and IP address, which information permitted Conducent to track the number of advertising impressions and “click-throughs” of ads.The information sent to Conducent’s ad servers also identified the eGames software product being used in order to serve appropriate ads, and to track the ad impressions and click-throughs served to the consumer by that product. These utilities had made use of your hard drive when downloading advertisements, create folders to store the files and other data and modify your Windows Registry.  This utility is not part of eGames’ software, but had been integrated into it solely for the purpose of serving and tracking advertisements. Conducent’s servers that the software attempts to contact for updates and reporting purposes are no longer active. 

**If you do not wish to make use of this technology, click _[here](http://www.egames.com/support/AdWare/index.htm)_ to access a Windows uninstall program to remove this utility from your computer.**

**Internet Links in Our Products  
  
**

Many of our products contain direct links to the Internet. The user needs to be connected to a full-service Internet Service Provider in order to visit the websites indicated on these products. The Internet can be accessed if the user “clicks” on the website buttons. If your computer is set up to link to the Internet automatically when the user clicks on a website “hyperlink”, your Internet connection will automatically be accessed when the website buttons are clicked on.

Some of our products access the Internet through the eGames browser. This browser and game interface is launched when the game is used, and it contains buttons that, when clicked on by the user, can access the Internet. The game play buttons do not access the Internet. 

If a user clicks on one of the buttons with Internet access, a screen may open asking the user to identify from which retail store the user purchased the product. If the user’s computer is set up to accept cookies, our server will send a cookie to the user’s computer, which cookie stores (1) the UPC code of the product, (2) the selected retailer identification, and (3) an expiration date for the cookie. If a user’s computer is set up not to accept cookies, the user will be directed to the eGames web site, as default, whenever the browser buttons are clicked.

**Use of IP Addresses**  

An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers -- the computers that "serve up" Web pages to your computer- automatically identify your computer by its IP address. eGames collects IP addresses for the purpose of tracking visitors’ usage of our site. We do not link IP addresses to any personally identifiable information, which means that a user's session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us.  Personally identifiable information includes name, address, phone number and email address. 

**Advertising on our Website**

eGames uses a third-party online advertising service company, Fastclick.com, Inc., to display advertisements throughout the eGames website.  Fastclick is responsible for maintaining and displaying the advertisements you may see on our website. 

Fastclick uses cookies to collect data from browsers to aggregate statistical information. This includes IP addresses, browser types, operating systems, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of Fastclick. Fastclick does not, and cannot, collect personally identifiable information about visitors to our website, such as email address, name, phone number and street address.

For more information about Fastclick.com, Inc., and their technology, or to opt-out of receiving cookies via their advertisements, please view their privacy policy on their website at <http://www.fastclick.com/co_privacy.html>

**Children’s Guidelines**  

eGames encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the activities offered by our website. No information should be submitted to or posted at eGames.com by customers under 13 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian. All customers under the age of 13 are required to have a parent register products online for them. We currently do not collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13.

**Links to Other Sites**  

Users should be aware that when they are at eGames.com, they could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from eGames web pages that take you outside our website. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement, the "click" takes you off the eGames site. This includes links to advertisers, website traffic auditing services, e-commerce service providers and co-branding partners. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. The eGames privacy policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond the control of eGames.

**Your Consent**   

By using this website, you consent to this privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our website.

**Changes to this Policy**  

Here at eGames, we continuously work to expand and improve the eGames.com website. When new features are added, we will incorporate the information collection and use practices stated in the policy. We will post any changes to this privacy policy at least 14 days prior to the change taking effect unless otherwise required by law.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact us at [webmaster@egames.com](mailto:%20webmaster@egames.com).
